(
"ai_sub_version": "3.0.2",
"generated_at": "2026-07-02T00:31:59.613475",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 15,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
Yeah, this is Flow Glow from hololive DEV_IS!
お待たせしました！
Thank you for waiting!
Flow Glow 3Dお披露目ライブ、Make It, Break It！
Flow Glow's 3D Showcase Live, 'Make It, Break It'!
楽しむ準備、できてますかー！？
Are you all ready to have some fun?!
搭載V8エンジン
V8 engine mounted!
第7感持ってる原人
Cavemen possessing the 7th sense!
Lockするこの世界と全人類
Locking down this world and all humanity!
この5人でゲームをチェンジ
These five of us are changing the game!
唸る4輪発射セヨ
Roaring 4 wheels, launch!
皆さん3キューサランヘヨ
Thank you, and I love you all!
操る2台のturntable
Controlling two turntables!
獲る1番ここground 0 (aye)
Taking first place, right here at ground zero!
リスク超えて挑戦
Challenging beyond the risk!
チャンスもセットだ当然
And taking chances as a package deal, of course!
登り上げる頂点
Climbing up to the peak!
座布団積んでく笑点
Piling up cushions like in Shoten!
乗り込むFG ROADSTER
Boarding the FG ROADSTER!
特殊部隊集合能力者
Special forces, assemble the gifted ones!
この歴史に名を彫る彫刻家
Sculptors carving our names into history!
ぶっちぎりで置き去り後続車
Leaving the cars behind in the dust!
今高速でぶち抜けていく大気圏
Now breaking through the atmosphere at high speed!
エンジンからジェットの炎揺れている怪気炎
Jet flames swaying from the engine, a fierce boast!
眼下に広がる大地を越えていく回帰線
Crossing the tropic line above the vast land!
バックミラーにbig blueが写っているIBM
The Big Blue is reflected in the rearview mirror!
(fire!)
打ち上げ台から飛んでく
Launching from the pad!
うちら世代この燃料
Our generation, this fuel!
朽ち果てないです銀河で
We will never decay in this galaxy!
寿司食べたい
I want to eat sushi!
見えてるでかいビジョン
I see a grand vision!
燃えてるメンバー一同
All members are burning up!
ただいま現在進行形
Right now, in real-time,
超えてく世界規模
we are going beyond global scale!
叶うはずだwon't stop
It's bound to happen, we won't stop!
心臓がモンスター
Our hearts are monsters!
aliens turn it up
FG party hard
光るtesla roadster
Glowing Tesla Roadster!
heavy booster
目覚めていく本能
Awakening instincts!
青い炎
Blue flame!
bff let's go out, so get in the car
0から宇宙まで囚われず
Unshackled from zero to outer space,
走るFG ROADSTER
running FG ROADSTER!
唸るbooster
Roaring booster!
flow glow the space to be
今chase me
Now chase me!
フログミのみんな、楽しんでますかー！？
Everyone in Flogmi, are you having fun?!
FGっ子たちも、もっともっとかます準備できてるー？！
Are you FG fans ready to kick it up even more?!
FG ROADSTERに続いては、この曲。24K GOLD！
Following 'FG ROADSTER' is this song... '24K GOLD'!
我々は翔るスーパーカー
We are racing in a supercar!
金ピカの光異次元
Flashy golden light from another dimension!
荒れ果てた世界パトロール
Patrolling the ruined world!
解き放て踊れ
Unleash and dance!
私たち存在が純金
Our very existence is pure gold!
いつでも万端な準備
Always fully prepared!
まるで無敵の宇宙人
Just like invincible aliens!
春麗よりも俊敏
More agile than Chun-Li!
最後ブレイクナイト突撃
Last break, night assault!
ハイボルテージ毎度素敵
High voltage, awesome every time!
最速です I will clear
With the fastest speed, I will clear!
今のっかってる波の上
Now riding on top of the wave!
変人凡人才人も
Weirdos, ordinary folks, and geniuses alike!
みんなで遊ぼう最近どう？
Let's hang out, how have you been?
流れてるflow like合気道
Our flow is like Aikido!
戦闘力マイティー・ソー (雷神！)
Power level like Thor (Thunder God!)
純度100%
100% purity!
この爆発力マクラーレン
This explosive power is like a McLaren!
メッキに興味ないルパン三世
Lupin III has no interest in cheap plating!
この輝きならツタンカーメン
With this brilliance, it's Tutankhamun!
髪風受けなびかせ
Letting our hair flutter in the wind,
good, good, groove your body / let it rock, rock, rock, rock, rock, rock on
good, good, groove your body / let it rock, rock, rock...
心を突き動かせ
Stir your heart,
good, good, groove your body / level up, up, up, up, up, up
good, good, groove your body / level up, up, up...
look at me now
身に纏うflight suitは24K GOLD
The flight suits we wear are 24K GOLD!
ready to go
深い闇照らす輝き24K GOLD
A brightness shining through deep darkness, 24K GOLD!
ready to go
空飛んでいるwassup
Flying in the sky, wassup!
このケープが翼
This cape is my wings!
漲っているpower
Power is overflowing!
戦ってるsuper girl
The fighting super girls!
全身駆け巡る満タンのガソリン
Full tank of gasoline coursing through the body!
黄金の流星だパッと見
At first glance, a golden meteor!
忍者みたい半蔵服部
Like a ninja, Hanzo Hattori!
強くて可愛くってかっこいい
Strong, cute, and cool!
戦う高鳴る
Fighting, high-spirited!
黄金の戦士現る
The golden warrior appears!
渋谷新宿原宿
Shibuya, Shinjuku, Harajuku!
風となりちはやぶる
Becoming the wind, running wild!
絶対撤退命令ない
No absolute withdrawal orders!
アベンジャーズみたいな精鋭隊
An elite squad like the Avengers!
生成AIにはないオーラ
An aura that generative AI doesn't have!
纏ってる輝く生命体
Wearing it, we are shining lifeforms!
髪風受けなびかせ
With my hair fluttering in the wind,
good, good, groove your body
let it rock, rock, rock, rock, rock, rock on
心を突き動かせ
Push your heart to move
good, good, groove your body
level up, up, up, up, up, up
look at me now
身に纏うflight suitは
The flight suit I'm wearing is...
24K gold
ready to go
深い闇照らす
Illuminating the deep darkness
輝き
with brilliance,
解き放て Let's go!
unleash! Let's go!
金色の戦士 FG fight up
Golden warrior, FG fight up
FG!
FLOW GLOW!
フローグロウ 3Dライブお披露目をごらんの皆様！
To everyone watching the FLOW GLOW 3D Live debut!
What's up!
きー！ろー！い！フローグロウです！
Ki-! Ro-! I-! We are FLOW GLOW!
先ほどは、FG Roadstarと24K GOLDをメドレー形式でお届けしました！
Earlier, we brought you a medley of FG Roadstar and 24K GOLD!
ありがとうございまーす！
Thank you so much!
いや、最初からど派手な登場すぎませんか？
I mean, wasn't that entry way too flashy right from the start?
まあね、どうやったらみんなをワッと驚かせられるか、考えた結果だよね
Well, that's what we came up with trying to think of how to surprise everyone.
そう、そう、一番ど派手なもんでいこうって言って、モニターを突き破ってきました！
Yeah, yeah! We said, 'Let's go with the flashiest option,' and crashed right through the monitor!
やりすぎ、やりすぎ
Overkill, overkill!
事故ってないよね？
No one got into an accident, right?
まあね、そんなハチャメチャすぎる私たちなんですけど、まずは自己紹介の方からさせていただけたらなと思います！
Well, as crazy as we are, we'd like to start with our self-introductions!
それでは私から！
Let's start with me!
私の隣、空いて、出会わない？ in the house！フローグロウのリーダー、伊咲りおなです！ぶらぶらー！
Is the seat next to me empty? Won't you meet me? In the house! FLOW GLOW's leader, Isaki Riona here! Bla-bla-!
次はにこ！
Next is Niko!
にこたそが、きたー！
Niko-taso is here!
ホロライブDEV_IS、フローグロウのお笑い担当、虎金弥衣子です！にこたそだにょ！
From Hololive DEV_IS, FLOW GLOW's comedy representative, Kogane Niko! I'm Niko-taso!
すーちゃん！
Su-chan!
ちゅぴしわす、すーの充電足りてる？ホロライブDEV_IS、フローグロウのエライセクシー担当、水宮すうです！
Chupishiwazu! Do you have enough Su-charge? From Hololive DEV_IS, FLOW GLOW's super-sexy representative, Mizumiya Su!
次はちは！
Next is Chihaya!
はい！エンジン全開、レッツゴー！フローグロウのDJ兼運転手担当、輪堂千早です！今日も盛り上がっていこうね！
Yes! Full engine, let's go! FLOW GLOW's DJ and driver representative, Rindo Chihaya! Let's get hyped today too!
次はビビ！
Next is Vivi!
はい！いきますよ！せーの、うーービビ！
Yes! Here we go! One, two, u-- Vivi!
いつもキラキラな綺々羅々ヴィヴィです！みんな今日も盛り上がっていきましょう！よろしく！
Always sparkling, Kikirara Vivi here! Everyone, let's get hyped today! Nice to meet you!
よろしくおねがいしまーす！
Nice to meet you!
今日は私たち5人で最高のライブをお届けしていくぞ！
Today, the five of us are going to deliver the best live show!
さて、すでにお気づきかと思いますが、ついにフローグロウも3Dデビューしました！
Now, you might have noticed already, but FLOW GLOW has finally made its 3D debut!
そりゃ気づくよね、これだけ動いてたらね<
Of course they'd notice, with us moving around this much!
ちなみにビビ、3Dになった自分の身体を見てどう思いますか？
By the way, Vivi, what do you think of your 3D body?
いやー、こんなにキューティー・セクシー・ヘルシーでね、みんなもっとビビのこと好きになっちゃったなぁ、ほんま！
Oh, being this cute, sexy, and healthy, everyone is going to fall even more in love with Vivi, seriously!
なんなん、このケツまじで
What is up with this butt, seriously?
お尻が...
That butt...
お尻触らないで！
Don't touch my butt!
触りたくなっちゃうよ
I can't help wanting to touch it!
交通事故になるから、マイクで叩きます！
We're going to have an accident, so I'll hit you with my mic!
はい、ありがとね。ちははどう？
Alright, thanks. What about you, Chihaya?
はい、ちははもちろん、この太もも！
Yes! For me, of course, it's these thighs!
ご覧ください！
Take a look!
みんな見て！
Everyone, look!
太もももっとくれ！
Give us more thighs!
触っていい？
Can I touch them?
ちはといえば、これで決まってんだよな。美脚タイプだからね。
That's classic Chihaya. You're the beautiful-legs type, after all.
すーちゃんはどうですか？
What about Su-chan?
はい、すーはま、かっこいいかな？みたいな。やっぱイケてるかな？みたいなね。
Yes, I guess I look pretty cool, right? Like, pretty stylish, maybe?
いや、水宮ってかっこいい...
I mean, Mizumiya is so cool...
いやいや、そんなキャラじゃなかったよ
No way, you weren't that kind of character!
漏れちゃったな、水宮
It slipped out, Mizumiya.
低い！低い！
So low! So low!
にこたそは？
What about Niko-taso?
にこたん完全にトラ。
Niko-tan is completely a tiger.
え？
Eh?
さっきまで二足歩行じゃなかった？
Weren't you walking on two legs just now?
やだ、ライブで踊るからそれ四足にはできないでしょ
No way, we have to dance, so you can't be on all fours!
そんな飛ばして、リオナはどうですか？
Moving on, what about you, Riona?
あ、そうですね。まああの、私も、超セクシーな...
Ah, let's see. Well, I also became super sexy...
セクシーやん！
So sexy!
かっこいい！
So cool!
セクシーダンスをこの身体でお披露目できるかなと思うとすごく嬉しいです！
I'm so happy to think I can show off my sexy dance in this body!
素晴らしい！
Wonderful!
可愛い！
So cute!
そんな私たち5人でお届けする3Dライブ、そのハッシュタグについては、にこ、説明よろしくお願いします！
To get the word out about our 3D Live, Niko, please explain the hashtag!
はーい！今日の3Dライブのハッシュタグ、右上をご覧ください！
Alright! For today's 3D Live hashtag, please look at the top right!
ハッシュタグ、FG3Dライブ、です！
The hashtag is #FG3Dライブ!
スクショにこのハッシュタグを加えて、Xでたくさんポストしてください！
Add this hashtag to your screenshots and post them a lot on X!
お願いします！
Please do!
トレンド1位目指すぞ、らしいです
Apparently, we're aiming for number one trending!
ライブを見てくれているみんなね、ぜひコメントでこのFGちゃんたちに声援を送ってください。よろしくお願いします！
Everyone watching, please send some cheers to the FG girls in the comments. We're counting on you!
よろしくお願いします！
Thank you!
はい、にこありがとう！
Alright, thank you, Niko!
はい、そしてライブの後半には、サプライズや重大発表もありますので、
Also, in the second half of the concert, we have surprises and a major announcement,
ぜひ最後まで楽しんでいただけると嬉しいです！
so we hope you'll enjoy it to the very end!
お願いします！
Please enjoy!
まばたきしないでね！
Don't blink!
てかさ、ちはやさん
By the way, Chihaya-san...
何ですか？
Yes?
フグ太郎置いてるのマズいかな？
Isn't it bad to leave Fugutaro parked out there?
ダメなの？ / かっこいいよ！
Is it bad? / It looks cool though!
東京あの、路上駐車ダメ、警察来ちゃうよ、切られちゃうよ
Street parking is bad in Tokyo, they'll ticket you!
駐禁切られちゃうよ / 路上駐車ダメ、ダメ
We'll get a parking ticket! / No street parking!
おまわりさん来ちゃうから
Because the police will come!
やめなさい！ / だめだめ！
Stop it! / No, no!
だから、まあ、繋いどくから、止めてきてもらって
So we'll hold down the fort here, go park it.
あ、止めてきていい？
Ah, can I go park it?
交代してくれる？
Can you go instead?
もちろん、もちろん！ / 待ってるからね
Of course, of course! / We'll wait for you!
行ってきます！
I'm off!
じゃあ、次の曲いこうか！
Well, shall we go to the next song?
ね！
Yeah!
冗談はさておき、
Jokes aside,
1曲目から『FG Roadster』と『24K Gold』をメドレー形式でお送りしてきました！
we kicked off with a medley of "FG Roadster" and "24K Gold"!
なんと、その『FG Roadster』のサビの振り付けは、
And actually, the choreography for the chorus of "FG Roadster"...
すーちゃんがしてくれたんだよね！
...was done by Su-chan!
おぉー！
Whoa!
やっぱりね、ちょっとカッコいい感じで、あ、バイバイ！
Yeah, with a cool vibe... Ah, bye-bye!
路上駐車、守れよ！
Make sure you park legally!
そう、カッコいい感じでね、こっからの振りを私、作らせていただいたんですけど、
Right, I got to make the choreography from here with a cool style.
カッコいいよね！ / 好きだよ
It's so cool! / I love it!
皆さんにもね、ぜひいつか踊ってください。よろしくお願いします！
Everyone, please try dancing to it sometime!
よろしくお願いします！
Please do!
ビビたんはメドレーやってみてどうだった？
Vivi-tan, how was performing the medley?
やっぱりずっとね、みんなに初めて披露した時から、あ、リリースした時から、
Well, ever since we first showed everyone—ah, ever since we released it—
歌とダンス一緒に見てもらいたいなと思ってたから、
I always wanted everyone to see the song and dance together,
こうやってついに皆さんに見てもらうことができて、めっちゃ嬉しいです！
so I'm super happy that we finally got to show you like this!
カッコよかったやろ？
We looked cool, right?
カッコよかった！
You looked so cool!
にこはどうやった？
How about you, Niko?
にこも楽しかった！やっぱいろんな曲をさ、くっつけてね、踊るとかね。
I had fun too! Putting different songs together and dancing...
ちょっと今、頭真っ白で何喋ってるか全然わかんないや
Actually, my mind is blank right now, I don't know what I'm saying.
りおなはどうだった？
How about you, Riona?
そうだね、でもやっぱデビュー当、当、と、と、と、と、
Yeah, but after all, at our deb-deb-de-de-de...
デビュー当時ね！
At our debut!
緊張して、と、と、と、と、と...
I'm so nervous, de-de-de-de...
りおなちゃん！深呼吸！深呼吸！
Riona-chan! Deep breath! Deep breath!
(深呼吸)
(all taking deep breaths)
どうした？どうした？何してるの？
What's going on? What are you guys doing?
りおなが震えてるから助けてくれ
Riona is shaking, save us!
メドレーの感想ね、言いたかったんだけど、
I wanted to share my thoughts on the medley,
うち等緊張してボロボロになっちゃって...
but we got so nervous we messed up...
任せて！
Leave it to me!
やっぱりね、デビューしてから2曲、出したね、オリジナル曲を
After all, since our debut, we've released two original songs,
こうやって皆さんの前で動きがありでね、あの披露することができて、
and being able to perform them with choreography in front of everyone like this,
本当にね、素敵でしたし、もうこれからもね、Flow Glow のこと、
was really wonderful. And from now on, please continue...
ずっと、よろしくお願いします！
...to support Flow Glow forever!
早い早い！泣くの早い！まだ曲あるから！
Too early! You're crying too early! We still have more songs!
あ、もう一曲あるのね、これからこれから！
Ah, we have more? Right, this is just the beginning!
ありがとうね、でもちはや、ありがとう。あ、止めてきてくれたのもありがとう
Thank you though, Chihaya. And thank you for going to park it.
そうだよ、ちょっとね、なんかファンの人の車が多すぎて、
Yeah, actually, there were so many fans' cars...
全然空いてなくて
that there was no space at all.
ファンの人の車？！ / ファンのみんなも路上駐車しちゃダメだよ！
The fans' cars?! / Don't park on the street, guys!
帰りは気をつけようね、危ないからね
Be careful on your way home, it's dangerous.
じゃあ、そろそろみんなもライブ観たいのかなって思うので、次の曲に参りたいと思います
Now then, I think everyone wants to see the live show, so let's move on to the next song.
はーい！
Yay!
ついでに、モニターもなんか新しいものになりました！
By the way, the monitors have been upgraded to something new!
おぉー！
Whoa!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much!
じゃあね、まだまだライブは続くので、ますます盛り上がっていきましょう！
The live show still continues, so let's get even more hyped up!
それでは聴いてください、『LOAD』
Now please listen to: "LOAD".
読み込みが完了しました！
Loading completed!
1、2、3、Jump!
1, 2, 3, Jump!
世界中に配信するライブ ここはホロ
Broadcasting live to the world, this is Holo
80億の星のlights 照らす心
Lights of 8 billion stars illuminate the heart
通知がなる it's time to show my digital world
Notifications ringing, it's time to show my digital world
寝かせない朝まで カーソル合わせ文字の上
Won't let you sleep until morning, aligning the cursor over the characters
スタジオにいる今日も歌詞を書いてるノートに
I'm in the studio, writing lyrics in my notebook again today
変わる景色、相当 気づけばいたよ東京
The changing scenery, quite a lot, realized I've arrived in Tokyo
夜空をみる首都高 乗る月に向かうボート
Looking at the night sky, Shuto Expressway, boarding a boat heading to the moon
みんなに見せる証拠 力になれること、を
Showing everyone the proof, that I can be your strength
ネガなマインド捨て 見てるだけじゃ意味ない
Throwing away negative thoughts, just watching is meaningless
夢じゃなくなった夢
A dream that is no longer just a dream
負けず嫌いで有名
Famous for being competitive
どこにもない終点
An endpoint that doesn't exist anywhere
君と見た星空の下 届きそうな手
Under the starry sky I saw with you, hands that seem to reach out
このデバイスがあれば どこへでも
If you have this device, I feel like I can go anywhere
行ける気がするよ
I feel like I can go anywhere
続くone way
Continuing one way
stay with me by my side
遠いとこへ
To a distant place
2人で
Just the two of us
この地球からvirtual world
From this Earth to a virtual world
気にしない今何時
Don't care what time it is now
何万キロ離れても
No matter how many thousands of kilometers apart
my team flow glow
すぐ行動開始 チャット止まない24
Start taking action immediately, chat never stops 24/7
調子がいい今日 カメラにするはいチーズ
In good condition today, posing for the camera, cheese!
乗っ取ってる電波塔から
Broadcasting from the taken-over radio tower
放送する 世界に配信
Broadcasting, distributing to the world
みてみなこのスタイル
Look at this style
yeah 負ける気すらない
yeah, I don't even have the thought of losing
捨てていく無駄なpride
Throwing away useless pride
できるよこのくらい
I can do this much
みんなで今夜もparty all night
Everyone partying all night again tonight
日々日々に上がるprice
Price rising day by day
やれるならu better try
If you can do it, you better try
世界中に配信するライブ ここはホロ
Broadcasting live to the world, this is Holo
80億 of 星のlights 照らす心
Lights of 8 billion stars illuminate the heart
通知がなる it's time to show my digital world
Notifications ringing, it's time to show my digital world
寝かせない朝まで カーソル合わせ文字の上
Won't let you sleep until morning, aligning the cursor over the characters
スタジオにいる今日も歌詞を書いてるノートに
I'm in the studio, writing lyrics in my notebook again today
変わりゆく景色そっと 気づけばいたよ東京
The changing scenery, so softly... before I knew it, I was in Tokyo
夜空を見下すトーク 昇る月に向かうボート
A talk looking down at the night sky, a boat heading towards the rising moon
みんなに見せるよショー 力になれることを
I'll show everyone the show, and that I can be a source of strength
一世一度しかない
You only live once
どう生きるか全部キミにしたい
I want to dedicate how I live entirely to you
好きなように生きていける世界
A world where we can live just as we like
広げていけるこの視界
We can expand this vision of ours
にゃにゃにゃにゃにゃん バズるのしてあげるよ
Nya-nya-nya-nya-nyan! I'll make you go viral!
音が狂いだす
The sound starts going wild
フィルターの針を
Set the filter's needle
踊れ Let's Party Go!
Dance, let's party go!
世界中に配信するライブ ここはホーム
Streaming live all over the world, this is home
80億 of 星の毎日 照らすコントロール
Controlling the light that shines on 8 billion stars daily
通知が鳴り止まないショウは デッドオアアライブ
The notifications won't stop ringing in this live-or-die show
ハチャメチャなアタマで 波長合わせ文字の上
With a chaotic mind, syncing wavelengths on top of the text
100万人の今日も 価値を変えてるノートに
Changing the value of today for a million people, in my notes
変わりゆく景色そっと 気づけばいたよ東京
The changing scenery, so softly, before I knew it, I was in Tokyo
夜空を見下すトーク 昇る月に向かうボート
A talk looking down at the night sky, a boat heading towards the rising moon
みんなに見せるよショー 力になれることを
I'll show everyone the show, and that I can be a source of strength
パジャマのままジョインする morning meeting
Joining the morning meeting still in my pajamas
頭空っぽになる my ルーティン
My mind goes blank, that's my routine
始まりから終わりまで mute screen
From start to finish, it's a mute screen
scree-scree-screen
起きれた私、えらい
I'm proud of myself for waking up
傘を持てた私、えらい
I'm proud of myself for bringing an umbrella
ネガティブはありえない
No need for negativity
自由に気分をリライト
Freely rewriting my mood today
背伸びしない、遠慮しない
No stretching too far, no holding back
やばいくらい 緩い my vibe
Incredibly loose, my vibe
描いたカラープッシュしたい
I want to push the colors I drew
オチのない話続ける
A genius who keeps narrating without a punchline
奇才、奇才、決めないでフリースタイル
A genius, genius, freestyling without deciding
指差されても気分はフライ
Even if they point fingers, my mood is fly
眠たい眠たい眠らない tonight
Sleepy, sleepy, but I won't sleep tonight
無敵の状態
Invincible state
態度でかいのは長所に変えて行けとお母さんが言ってた
My mom told me to turn a big attitude into a strength
フィルター越しのスナップでピース
Giving a peace sign through a filtered snap
本当のことは虹の彼方に
The truth's somewhere beyond the rainbow
リアルもフェイクも just like a piece
Both real and fake are just like a piece
So decide what is real
イケてないけど good, good enough
Not cool, but good good enough
明日も good, good, good enough
Tomorrow too, good good good enough
ちょっとルーズだけど good, good enough
A little loose, but good good enough
明日も good, good, good enough
Tomorrow too, good good good enough
目標高くても good, good enough
Even if my goals are high, good good enough
明日も good, good, good enough
Tomorrow too, good good good enough
イケてないけど good, good enough
Not cool, but good good enough
明日も good, good, good enough
Tomorrow too, good good good enough
誤字脱字は日常茶飯事
Typos and mistakes are part of daily life
また見落とし、寝過ごし、それも生きてる証
Overlooking and oversleeping again, it's just proof that I'm alive
未完成だからこそ作れる
Because it's incomplete, we can create
Good, good enough
磨けば必ず光るぜって
If you polish it, it will surely shine
Good, good enough
夢見てた頃の自分は最強
The me who dreamed was the strongest
まで集めたフル装備でファイト
Fighting with the full gear I've collected up to now
ビビりだからこそ高めるマインド
Because I'm a coward, I build up my mind
褒めたい褒めたい、たまに褒められたい
I wanna praise myself, and sometimes be praised in kind
言葉じゃ足りない
Words aren't enough
愛想が良いのは赤ちゃんの時からっておばあちゃんも言ってた
My grandma told me my friendliness is from when I was a baby
パジャマのままジョインする morning meeting
Joining the morning meeting still in my pajamas
頭空っぽになる my ルーティン
My mind goes blank, that's my routine
始まりから終わりまで mute screen
From start to finish, it's a mute screen
So, who decides what we are
イケてないけど good, good enough
Not cool, but good good enough
明日も good, good, good enough
Tomorrow too, good good good enough
ちょっとルーズだけど good, good enough
A little loose, but good good enough
明日も good, good, good enough
Tomorrow too, good good good enough
目標高くても good, good enough
Even if my goals are high, good good enough
明日も good, good, good enough
Tomorrow too, good good good enough
目標高くても good, good enough
Even if my goals are high, good good enough
明日も good, good, good enough
Tomorrow too, good good good enough
フィルター越しのスナップでピース
Giving a peace sign through a filtered snap
本当のことは虹の彼方に
The truth’s somewhere beyond the rainbow
リアルもフェイクも just like a piece
Both real and fake are just like a piece
So decide what is real
パジャマのままジョインする morning meeting 頭空っぽになる my ルーティン
Joining the morning meeting in pajamas, my mind goes blank, that's my routine
始まりから終わりまで mute screen 始まりから終わりまで mute screen
From start to finish, it's a mute screen... from start to finish, it's a mute screen
Oh yeah...
La la la yeah...
Once upon a time...
...there was a little girl...
君によく似た
...who really looked like you.
Oh darling...
君に似てた
...she was just like you.
彼女はまるでタイガーアイ
She was just like a tiger's eye.
無数の欲より大事な
More precious than any kind of greed...
夢を見つけては
...she found herself a dream...
掴んでしまった
...and she made it hers.
ある夜雨が降ってた
One night, it was raining...
濡れた瞳にぼやけた
...and her dewy eyes saw a blurry sight.
嘘のように美しい
Like a beautiful lie,
ダリアが微笑んでた
a dahlia was smiling.
I was the same one.
それが欲しいのと吐き捨てこう言った
That's what she wanted, she spat out and said.
引き換えに何が欲しい?
'What do you want in return?'
奏でろ賛美歌
Now go on and play that hymn.
無知なメロディーはハイ
A melody of ignorance is a high.
たかが心なら
If all you want is my heart,
差し上げたいわ
I'd love to give it away.
And then I 甘ったるい願いね
And then I... what a sweet wish.
そして彼女は
And then she was...
ただダリアのように
...just like a dahlia.
No, ダリア
No, dahlia...
改めまして、千崎ダリアです！
Once again, I'm Chisaki Dahlia!
名前、覚えて帰ってください！
Please remember my name before you leave!
乱心 内心 邁進 ego
Inner chaos, inner drive, moving forward, ego...
up & down always get into trouble
「楽しい」「正しい」「嬉しい」でも
Even if it's 'fun', 'correct', or 'happy',
平常 me、sold out
normal me is sold out.
あれナシ これナシ
Without this, without that...
合わせる 段々 敵なし
...conforming, step by step, with no enemies.
己の way?
My own way?
違える (no, no)
Wrong (no, no)
またゼロへ get away (oh no, no, no...)
Back to zero, get away (oh no, no, no...)
Whisper to my ears
Oh give me some more details
手招き 脱して、勝ち
Beckoning, breaking out, win!
No way slipping and breaking down
かませ 急上昇
Let it loose, rapid rise!
はなて 絶好調 own way now
Let it go, peak condition, own way now!
Better show what I gotta gotta show!
Ima shake it, let's go. Next!
変幻 理想像
Fanciful ideal figure...
Come again, 熱狂
...come again, enthusiasm!
Hey show me what you got
I'm breaking down pretty me
Next side, next side...
楽しんだれ up boomboom!
Enjoy it, up boomboom!
Trip in the dark...
such a funny thing for me to explain
It's ok even if you don't understand
I just wanna make you roll
ルールはない unchain
There are no rules, unchain!
頭と心 awake now
Head and heart, awake now!
アブラカタ blah blah blah 幻なら
Abrakadabra, blah blah blah, if it's an illusion...
無理×3 価値なし 無視 ah just do it!
...impossible x3, no value, ignore, ah just do it!
Are you ready, let's play game!!
万人万事 愛しては
Loving ten thousand people and ten thousand things,
一蓮托生 三千世界
we share our fate, three thousand worlds!
Dancing 突進 童心 get up
Dancing, rushing, childlike, get up...
全方位 call out
...all directions, call out!
人生も 来世も
Life and next life...
I wish days were longer than 24
曇りなく いたいの yeah
I want to remain cloudless, yeah.
I'm feeling really mellow
Oh I wanna feel more
たまには わがままに
...sometimes, be selfish.
Now hey, come in and turn it loud
鳴らせ 鼓動を
Sound the heartbeat!
醒ませ 最高潮 own way now
Awaken to the climax, own way now!
Better show what I gotta gotta show...
Gotta show what I wanna wanna show!
Ima shake it, let's go. Next!
変幻 理想像
Fanciful ideal figure...
Come again, 熱狂
...come again, enthusiasm!
Hey show me what you got
I'm breaking down pretty me
Next side, next side...
楽しんだれ up boomboom!
Enjoy it, up boomboom!
Na na na yeah...
Na na na na na na na na...
Let's make it loud!
La-ta-ta-tat!
Next side, next side...
楽しんだれ up boomboom!
Enjoy it, up boomboom!
Yeah, yeah, yeah...
一度はあの光を見たんだよ とてもキレイで
I once saw that light, it was so beautiful.
でも今思えば汚かった あれはいわゆるBad Day Dreams
But thinking about it now, it was dirty, it was what they call Bad Day Dreams.
光が眩し過ぎて周りが見えず ただただ日々を
The light was too dazzling, I couldn't see my surroundings, just wasting my days...
棒に振ってたあの日 今だから笑えるよ
Those days, I can laugh about them now.
一度はあの幕を開けたんだよ とても重くて
I once opened that curtain, it was so heavy.
プレッシャー、イヤ味それに勝つために ただ嫌なヤツで
Just to win against the pressure and snide remarks, I was just a nasty person.
そして気が付くと真っ暗な部屋に 一人ぼっちだった
And when I noticed, I was all alone in a pitch-black room.
終わった... もう戻れない... なんて... 歩くのも止めた...
It's over... I can't go back... or so I thought... I even stopped walking...
でもI'm not alone. I'm not alone
But I'm not alone. I'm not alone.
We're not, We're not, We're not alone
お金じゃ買えないもの手に入れて
I got something money can't buy,
もう一度光浴びて そして今度は騙されぬように
bathed in the light once more, and this time, so I won't be deceived,
僕らは今目指すよ 欲望に満ちた青年団
we are aiming now, the youth group filled with desire.
誰かが言った言葉 それすらその時は流して
The words someone said, I just let them pass at the time.
今になって気付いたよ 欲望に負けた少年団
Now I've realized, the youth group that lost to desire.
So, I know you know, You know, I know
We have, we have, we have along
囚われないように遠く向いて
Facing far away so I won't be trapped,
歩く
I walk.
もう一度光浴びて そして今度は騙されぬように
Bathed in the light once more, and this time, so I won't be deceived,
僕らは今目指すよ 欲望に満ちた青年団
we are aiming now, the youth group filled with desire.
誰かが言った言葉 それすらその時は流して
The words someone said, I just let them pass at the time.
今になって気付いたよ 欲望に負けた少年団
Now I've realized, the youth group that lost to desire.
Hey...
Oh... Oh...
ありがとうございました
Thank you very much.
んー、おはよ
Mmm, good morning.
朝起きてまず確認 きょうもいい感じだね
Wake up in the morning and check first, looking good today too.
一年365日 わたしのこと一番みてるひと
365 days a year, the one who looks at me the most.
好きですと言えるのは 当たり前とかじゃない
Being able to say "I like you", it's not a matter of course.
一日86400秒
86,400 seconds a day...
ずっと付き合ってくんだから
Because we're always going to be together.
ママから聞いたことあるわ
I've heard from my mom before...
似た人を好きになるんじゃなくて
It's not that you fall in love with someone similar.
好きな人には似るものらしいです 本当です
It seems you start to resemble the one you love, it's true.
みんな思ったことあるわ
Everyone has thought about it before.
目を開けたら違う自分になって
Opening your eyes and becoming a different self...
いやいやもっと真剣に変身
No, no, transform more seriously!
マスカラのない夜　フルフルル
Night without mascara, fluff, fluff, fluff.
あれ可愛くなりすぎちゃったかも
Maybe I've become too cute?
さすがに盛りすぎちゃったかも
Maybe I've overdone the makeup a bit?
あなたの真似したんです
I just copied what you did.
だって　超大好きなんですから
Because I really love you so much!
鏡よ鏡もちょっとだけ
Mirror, mirror, just a little bit...
可愛くなってもいいのかな
Is it okay if I become cute?
いつだって　正直にいって Mommy
Always be honest with me,
あなたのことだけは歌ってほしい
I want you to sing of nothing but you,
ならば私は戦える
if so, then I can fight,
たとえこの耳が聞こえないとしても
even if these ears can no longer hear.
思い馳せなくなっていた
I had stopped letting my thoughts wander,
虹を覚えてる空には
to the sky that still remembers the rainbow,
くたびれた靴が響くよ
but the sound of worn-out shoes echoes.
それでも歩いていると
Even so, as I keep walking,
掴もうとしてすり抜けた
the words that slipped away as I tried to grasp them...
言葉、忘れない手のひら
I won't forget them in the palm of my hand.
指を二つにして隠した
Crossing my fingers to hide the magic
強さに変える魔法を
that turns them into strength.
あぁ、どれだけ息をしたら
Ah, how many breaths must I take
「これでよかった」と思える？
before I can believe it was all for the best?
心がずっと砕けながら
Even as my heart is constantly shattered,
欠片の全部で動いてる
it moves with every single one of its pieces.
これはきっと帰り道
This is surely the road back home.
あの日と同じじゃなくていい
It doesn't have to be the same as that day.
ただもう一度だけ会いたい
I just want to meet you one more time.
何も怖くはない
I am not afraid of anything anymore.
泣かないでって祈るのは
Praying "please don't cry" are
足元の明日の涙
the tears of tomorrow at my feet.
迷いを乗せた爪先で
With toes carrying my doubts,
進め、進め、魂ごと
move forward, move forward, along with my soul!
正しいかどうか、なんてことよりも
Rather than whether it's right or wrong,
あなたのいる世界が笑ってほしい
I want the world you live in to smile.
だから私は生きている
That is why I am living,
時計の針にも奪えない力を
with a power that not even the hands of time can steal.
不意に会った宝物が
The shadows cast by the treasures
落とす影、まだ探してる
I met by chance... I'm still searching.
あぁ、もう一度だけ会いたい
Ah, I just want to meet you one more time.
何も怖くはない
I am not afraid of anything anymore.
命は理由に出会えた
My life has found its reason.
燃えて消える意味を知った
I've learned the meaning of burning away.
その陽が視界を照らした
That light illuminated my vision,
青く、青く、どこまでも
blue, blue, endlessly.
明日がすべてを失っても
Even if tomorrow loses everything,
繋いだことだけは歌ってほしい
I want you to sing of nothing but our connection.
だから私は生きている
That is why I am living,
欠片の全部で、永遠
with every piece of me, for eternity.
泣かないでって祈るのは
Praying "please don't cry" are
足元の明日の涙
the tears of tomorrow at my feet.
迷いを乗せた爪先で
With toes carrying my doubts,
進め、進め、魂ごと
move forward, move forward, along with my soul!
間違いかどうか、なんてことよりも
Rather than whether it's a mistake or not,
あなたのいる世界が続いてほしい
I want the world you live in to continue.
ならば私は戦える
If so, then I can fight,
たとえその時、傍にいなかったとしても
even if I am not by your side at that time.
Sarracenia
[Song: Sarracenia]
この地球上すべてのゲームが上の空かい？
Is every game on this Earth just a distraction?
半端な格好で臨むなよ坊や
Don't approach with a half-hearted attitude, boy.
リアルなビースト気取りのプリマドンナ
Real beasts posing as primadonnas...
フッ、話になんねぇ
Hah, you're not even worth talking to.
何でそんなに自信があるんですか？
Why are you so confident?
骨の髄まで負けた結果が当たり前じゃん
The result of losing to the bone is obvious, right?
ジャマなビースト気取りの皮肉屋
An annoying beast posing as a cynic...
フッ、話になんねぇ
Hah, you're not even worth talking to.
多くを喰らえ
Eat a lot,
胃袋を肥え
fatten your stomach.
目に物見せてきな 味わい尽くせ
Show them what you've got, savour it to the fullest!
飢え、雨、まどろみ
Hunger, rain, slumber...
思い描いてどうしたい？
What do you want to do with what you pictured?
ただ手にする代わりは幾らですか？
What is the price of just getting it?
憂うな、超えろ
Do not grieve, overcome it!
そこから上を向けよ
Look up from there!
リアルに飢えろ、飢えろ、ねぇ
Really starve, starve! Hey,
もっとここまで来いよ
come further up here!
噛み堪え、噛み堪え
Bite and endure, bite and endure!
夢を越えろ
Go beyond dreams
whoa
ここまで来いよ
Come this far
頭冷やすリスク、リスクがたまんない
The risk of cooling my head is irresistible
安定も安心も手伝いにはなんない
Neither stability nor security will help
次にやる予定もテメェの好きにやりな
Do what you plan to do next however you like
あぁ 離すなよ baby
Ah, don't let go, baby
もうちょい遊んで頂戴
Please play with me a little more
馬鹿にしてるって？とんでもねぇ
You think I'm making fun of you? No way
バイキング食べ放題 ただ毒に当たってもドンマイ
All-you-can-eat buffet, but don't mind even if you get poisoned
お味の方は いかがですか？
How does it taste?
夢を越えろ
Go beyond dreams
そこから
From there...
上を向けよ
...look up
本物に飢えろ 飢えろ
Hunger for authenticity, hunger
yeah
whoa ここまで来いよ
whoa, come this far
完膚なきまで 完膚なきまで
Completely, utterly
完膚なきまで 完膚なきまで yeah
Completely, utterly, yeah
夢を越えろ
Go beyond dreams
whoa ここまで来いよ
whoa, come this far
待てない 待たない いくらあっても足りない
Can't wait, won't wait, no matter how much, it's not enough
腹いっぱい 食べたい 手前をやっときな さらり
I want to eat my fill, just do your thing smoothly
格の差ボトボト 脳内暴動 欲しいものはゲトるのが作法
The gap in class is dripping, brain riot, getting what I want is etiquette
合図も行動もクローズ スモーク兆候 超一級のフルコース
Signals and actions closed, smoke, signs, a super first-class full course
数字と結果は当然 出口ごとぶっ潰す
Numbers and results are natural, I'll destroy even the exits
お近くどうぞ もっと勝負勝負 勝つのは
Come closer, play more, the one who wins is...
ストップの時で凍ってたトップの奪い合い
...clashing for the top that was frozen in stopped time
夢を越えろ
Go beyond dreams
そこから上を向けよ
Look up from there
リアルに飢えろ 飢えろ
Hunger for reality, hunger
whoa ここまで来いよ
whoa, come this far
完膚なきまで 完膚なきまで
Completely, utterly
夢を越えろ
Go beyond dreams
whoa ここまで来いよ
whoa, come this far
完膚なきまで 完膚なきまで
Completely, utterly
夢を越えろ
Go beyond dreams
whoa ここまで来いよ
whoa, come this far
あれが正解なんて
Are you sure that was the correct answer?
誰の成れの果て？
Whose end did it come to?
答えも欲しいのも一個てこれだけ
The answer and what I want is only this one
悩んだってしょうがないじゃんね
There's no point in worrying, is there?
あれは夢だったって思うことにしたって
Even if I decide to think it was just a dream
でも全然思えないんだけど
But I can't think that at all
助けてよフォロワー！
Help me, follower!
抗うだけ若さに負け
Just resisting, losing to youth
next, next, lucky, lucky & lucky!
アーリーオ 割り切れたらさ
Ah-li-o, if you could just get through it
オーリーオ 楽なのにとか
O-li-o, it would be easy...
もうやだ！
I've had enough!
なんていう新世界か！
What kind of new world is this?!
あなた以外は あなた以外はいらない ない ない
I don't need anyone but you, anyone but you
はらないでよバリア あるはずなの何か
Don't put up a barrier, there must be something
あったならば happy, jumpin', yeah
If you find it, happy, jumpin', yeah
あなたのその手と
Your hand...
あたしのこの手を
...and my hand
つないだらもう二度と離さないわ
If connected, I won't let go ever again
あなたのその手が
If your hand...
あたしのこの手を
...grabs my hand
掴んだら 以後お見知りおきを my love
From now on, nice to meet you, my love
しらけんが来たぞー！
Shiraken is here!
後半戦！レッツゴー！盛り上がっていくぞ！レッツゴー！
Second half! Let's go! Let's pump it up! Let's go!
しらけんの充電足りてる？足りてないよねー！後半戦も盛り上がっていくぞー！
Is your Shiraken charge full? Not enough, right? Let's pump up the second half too!
みんなのことをもっとメラメラにしちゃうぞ！後半戦もせーの、うー、にゃっぴー！
I'll make you all even more fired up! For the second half, ready, set, oo-nyappii!
みんなに出会えて、とっても幸せです！画面の向こうのみんな、声出してー！おらー！
I'm so happy to meet all of you! Everyone on the other side of the screen, make some noise! Let's go!
新しい姿のしらけんで、新しい曲！聴いてくれ、MAKE IT, BREAK IT！
With Shiraken's new look, a new song! Please listen, MAKE IT, BREAK IT!
Make it, break it, make it, break it, Make it, break it, look on!
パッと目が合えば I know 君こそが相棒
Once our eyes meet, I know you are my partner
メロディ奏でる才能は Make it, break it, make it, break it
Our talent for creating melodies is Make it, break it, make it, break it
パッと見 丁寧にしてても
Even if we seem polite at first glance,
中身は冷めてても
even if we are cold inside,
そのギャップと愛嬌あれば最強
with that gap and charm, we're the strongest!
平凡、お仕事、平穏そう？
Ordinary? Work? Looking peaceful?
一蓮托生は敵わない 退屈に用はない
Being in the same boat is unbeatable, I have no use for boredom!
一線画すよバディライン 届かない しょうがない
Drawing a line on our buddy line, you can't reach us, too bad!
追い風がするどい風に変わっても バディ、バディ！
Even if the tailwind turns into a sharp wind, buddy, buddy!
見惚れちゃうでしょ？ look at me, look at me now...
You're captivated, right? Look at me, look at me now...
置いてかない絶対 ついて来て 5mc's
I'll never leave you behind, follow us, 5MC's
本気のフライデーナイト
A serious Friday night
Make it! Break it!
make a revolution アタシを貫け
Make a revolution, pierce through me!
傾け 傾け
Be eccentric! Be eccentric!
夢に強引 going, going, going on!
Forcing my way into the dream, going, going, going on!
break through and never stop
真ん中ぶち抜け 抜け 抜け
Break through the absolute center, let's go!
can't get enough
you'll see! make it, break it!
make it? break it?
make it, break it!
bang! bang! bang!
you'll see! make it, break it!
make it? break it?
make it, break it!
ほら、どっちにするの？
So, which one will you choose?
有象無象沸かす flow glow
Boiling up the rabble, Flow Glow!
ay 口先より行動
Ay, actions speak louder than words!
if you wanna be マイメン
If you wanna be my men
よそ見とかナシで
No looking away!
warning! 没頭 ほら 没頭 ほら
Warning! Immerse yourself, look, immerse yourself, look!
味わっちゃって
Savor it!
burning! もっと hotter もっと hotter
Burning! More hotter, more hotter!
ハイになっちゃって
And get high!
置いてかない絶対 ついて来て 5mc's
I'll never leave you behind, follow us, 5MC's
本気のフライデーナイト
A serious Friday night
make it? break it?
brand new generation
感じるまま アガれ アガれ
As you feel it, get up, get up!
華麗に降臨 only, only one
Gracefully descending, only, only one!
退屈な neverland
A boring Neverland
速攻で抜け出せ i say
Get out of here instantly, I say!
ready or not?
you'll see! make it, break it!
make it? break it?
make it, break it!
bang! bang! bang!
you'll see! make it, break it!
make it? break it?
make it, break it!
朝まで make some noise
Make some noise until morning!
FG、行くぞ！
FG, let's go!
make a revolution アタシを貫け
Make a revolution, pierce through me!
傾け 傾け
Be eccentric! Be eccentric!
夢に強引 going, going, going on!
Forcing my way into the dream, going, going, going on!
break through and never stop
真ん中ぶち抜け 抜け 抜け
Break through the absolute center, let's go!
can't get enough
you'll see! make it, break it!
make it? break it?
make it, break it!
bang! bang! bang!
you'll see! make it, break it!
make it? break it?
make it, break it!
ほら、どっちにするの？
So, which one will you choose?
いよいよ、次が最後の曲です。聞いてください。stay by my side
Finally, the next is our last song. Please listen: stay by my side.
ずっと揺らせない みなとのファーストデイ
Always unshakable, the port's first day...
積もり声メイク あれはフェイクフェイス
Layered voice makeup, that's a fake face...
見せたくて作ったはりぼてに 期待と不安詰め込んで
I stuffed my expectations and anxieties into the papier-mache I made because I wanted to show it.
歩き出したんだ せーので
And we started walking on three...
強がってた淡い涙こらえ
I was acting tough, holding back my faint tears,
でも皆に気づかされた そのままでええやん
but everyone made me realize, it's fine just as it is.
型通りじゃつまらないこの日々
These days that are boring if they are just conventional,
バチャになっても一緒にいたい my beat
even if we are virtual, I want to be together, my beat.
気づいたら騒がしい毎日
Before I knew it, every day was noisy.
違う歩幅 どこに行くわたしたち
With different strides, where are we going?
迷う自分 皆くれる刺激
I'm lost, but everyone gives me stimulation.
なれ合いじゃない これって素敵？
It's not just playing along, isn't this wonderful?
まだリーダーって胸張れなくても
Even if I can't proudly call myself a leader yet,
持てる何かあるよ 糧なる覚悟
there is something I can hold, a resolve that becomes my nourishment.
チームのため歌って踊るステージ
A stage where I sing and dance for the team,
プログロー刻み込み めくる次のページ
carving in ProGlow, turning the next page.
stay by my side 夜中になってもまだ寝れない
stay by my side, even when it's midnight, I still can't sleep.
yeah あとどのくらい
Yeah, how much longer...
辿り着くあの夢の世界
...until we reach that dream world?
初めて会ったあの日 また輪になって遊んだり
That day we first met, playing together in a circle again,
ここまで歩いてきた
we've walked all the way here.
鮮明に今でも覚えてる
I still remember it vividly.
stay by my side 街角で二人
stay by my side, the two of us at the street corner.
by my side 考えてる一人
by my side, thinking all alone.
無駄にはならないからあの涙も
Because even those tears won't be in vain.
今ここ stay by my side
Right here, stay by my side,
寄り添ってる隣
snuggled up next to me.
ずっと昔 はぐれた炎
A flame that went astray a long time ago,
夜を必死に照らしたこと
desperately lighting up the night.
集まる星は重なったこと
The gathering stars overlapped.
それは波長 これからも残る音
That is the wave, the sound that will remain.
暗闇の中見えない 曖昧
The obscurity invisible in the darkness,
道しるべはあなたのサイン
your sign is the guidepost.
光よこの手を離さないで
Light, please don't let go of this hand,
空の始まりよりきらめいて保存
sparkle brighter than the beginning of the sky.
最初のストーリー 同じ夢追い
The first story, chasing the same dream,
相棒だし we もう一人じゃない
we're partners, we're not alone anymore.
隅々ヤバい プログローの宇宙
Every corner is amazing in ProGlow's universe.
可能性は未知数 取りま配信に夢中
The possibilities are infinite, for now obsessed with streaming.
いつか皆で行こうわい
Let's all go together someday!
聴けラララ セラピー VIP
Listen to the La-La-La therapy, VIP,
楽しみたい日々
every day we want to enjoy.
ロゴや名刺に込めた4人を
The four of us embedded in the logo or business card,
私たちはやれるきっとフロムリンドウ
we can definitely do it, from Rindo!
シナジー、足りてる？
Is the synergy enough?
足りてる！
It's enough!
レッツゴー！
Let's go!
いくぞー！
stay by my side 夜中になってもまだ寝れない
stay by my side, even when it's midnight, I still can't sleep.
yeah あとどのくらい
Yeah, how much longer...
辿り着くあの夢の世界
...until we reach that dream world?
初めて会ったあの日 また輪になって遊んだり保存
That day we first met, playing together in a circle again,
ここまで歩いてきた
we've walked all the way here.
鮮明に今でも覚えてる
I still remember it vividly.
上がれペース 夜も寝れず
Increase the pace, can't sleep at night,
置き去りにした生活リズム
leaving behind my lifestyle rhythm.
12ヶ月
12 months...
共にいた日々 振り返る
...looking back on the days we were together.
時に戻ったりしたっていいんじゃない？
Isn't it okay to return sometimes?
一喜一憂 強がりもない
Joy and anger, no acting tough,
一人で抱え込むなよ ほら面倒くさい
don't bottle it up alone, look, it's bothersome.
最後に自分らしく居りゃ心配ない
In the end, as long as you are yourself, there's no worry.
美味しいもん食べて 活気活気！
Eat delicious food, and be lively!
stay by my side 夜中になってもまだ寝れない
stay by my side, even when it's midnight, I still can't sleep.
yeah あとどのくらい
Yeah, how much longer...
辿り着くあの夢の世界
...until we reach that dream world?
初めて会ったあの日 また輪になって遊んだり
That day we first met, playing together in a circle again,
ここまで歩いてきた
we've walked all the way here.
いつまでもオーバーフローしてる
...but it's overflowing.
Stay by my side 街角のね 二人
Stay by my side, the two of us on the street corner
By my side 考えてる 一人
By my side, thinking all alone
無駄にはならないから あの涙も整う
Because they won't go to waste, those tears too
今ここ by my side 寄り添ってる隣
Right here, by my side, snuggling next to me
はい！ということで後半ノーストップで駆け抜けてきましたが
All right! So we've run through the second half non-stop, but...
ご覧の通り、衣装チェンジしてまーす！
...as you can see, we've changed our outfits!
イェーイ！
Yay!
いや本当に一人ひとり個性がめちゃくちゃ主張されていて素敵
No, seriously, everyone's individuality really shines through. It's wonderful!
にこちゃんはかっこいいし
Niko-chan is so cool,
りつちゃんはもうかっこ可愛くて、すずちゃんはもう可愛すぎるし
Ritsu-chan is cool and cute, and Suzu-chan is just too cute!
それに、なんてったって、ちひちゃん
And on top of that, Chihi-chan...
え？ え？
Eh? Me?
可愛いね
...is so cute.
なんやその言い方
What's with that way of saying it?!
ありがとう、そっちゃんも可愛いよ、にこも
Thanks, Socchan is cute too, and Niko as well.
みんなに言ってる！ みんなに言ってる！
She's saying that to everyone! To everyone!
なんと！ここで嬉しいお知らせがあります！
Guess what! We have some happy news here!
このFLOW GLOWの3Dお披露目ライブ
This FLOW GLOW 3D debut live...
なんとXのトレンドで1位になりました！
...has actually reached #1 on X's trending!
イェーイ！
Yay!
おい！おい！おい！おい！
Oi! Oi! Oi! Oi!
嬉しくて、嬉しくて
We're just so happy!
はい、それではここまでを振り返っていきたいと思います！
All right, now let's look back on what we've done so far!
まずは私、莉央奈が「ダリア」と「アップブーンブーン」のメドレーを披露させていただきました
First off, I, Riona, performed a medley of "Dahlia" and "Up Boom Boom"!
いただきましたじゃない、そこじゃない。もっとオブラートに包んで
Not "performed," that's not it. Wrap it in a softer tone.
ジャズダンスとバレエとガールズを披露させていただきました。セクシーだったかな？
I performed jazz dance, ballet, and girls' hip-hop. Was I sexy?
セクシーだったよ！
You were sexy!
はい、ちひゃはトロンボーンとギターを自分で弾きまして
Yes, I, Chihiha, played the trombone and guitar myself...
ギターの弾き語りで「欲に満ちた青年団」を歌わせていただきました
...and sang "Yoku ni Michita Seinendan" while playing the guitar!
練習してきたのでみんなに披露できて嬉しいです。聴いてくれてありがとう！
I've been practicing, so I'm glad I could show everyone. Thanks for listening!
そしてビビは、メイクを活かした「鏡」という楽曲を歌わせていただきました
And I, Bibi, sang the song "Kagami" (Mirror) while making use of my makeup!
メイクの変化見てくれた？
Did you see the change in my makeup?
可愛かった！
It was so cute!
あ、お尻見たの？
Ah, did you look at my butt?
お尻じゃない！ やめて！
Not your butt! Stop it!
はい、続いては？
All right, who's next?
にこちゃんは大好きなBUMP OF CHICKENさんの「青」を、昨日実は、ギターとタップです！
Niko-chan actually performed her favorite BUMP OF CHICKEN song, "Ao," yesterday with guitar and tap dancing!
ギタッパーです！実タッパーです！
A guitar-tapper! A live tapper!
色んな思いを込めて歌わせていただいたので、またアーカイブとか観てもらえたら嬉しいです。そしてお次は？
I sang it with many feelings, so I'd be happy if you could watch the archive. And next?
はーい、すずが「サラシニア」と「ギャル」のメドレーを躍らせていただきました！
Yes! Suzu performed a medley of "Sarracenia" and "Gal"!
結構かっこよく躍ったんだ
I danced pretty coolly!
かっこよかった！
You were cool!
今はどう？
How about now?
みんなでソロを楽しんでもらったあとは、私たちの新曲、そしてライブのタイトルにもなっております
After enjoying everyone's solos, we performed our new song, which is also the title of this live show...
「MAKE IT, BREAK IT」を初披露させていただきました！
... "MAKE IT, BREAK IT," for the very first time!
今日リリース...あ、これ言っちゃダメだ。忘れて！
Releasing today... ah, I shouldn't say that. Forget it!
そのあとは、私たちのこないだ出させていただいたシングル「Stay by my side」を披露させていただきました！
After that, we performed our recently released single, "Stay by my side"!
そして、ここで配信を見てくれているみんなにお知らせがあります！
And now, we have an announcement for everyone watching the stream!
私たちと同じ5つあるので、一人ひとり紹介させていただきたいと思います！
We have five announcements, just like our group members, so we'd like to introduce them one by one!
トップバッターはビビ、よろしく！
First up is Bibi. Go ahead!
はーい、それではこちらをご覧ください。どうぞ！
Yay! Well then, please take a look at this. Here you go!
ファーストアルバム「FLOW GLOW」についてです。発売日は来年1月21日！
It's about our 1st album "FLOW GLOW." The release date is January 21st next year!
デビュー曲「FG ROADSTER」のほか、気鋭のサウンドクリエイター陣が手掛ける全9曲を収録しています！
Along with our debut song "FG ROADSTER," it features 9 tracks produced by rising sound creators!
すごい！
Awesome!
通常盤はType-A、Type-Bあり、公式EC版と全国流通盤では特典内容も違います
The regular edition has Type-A and Type-B, and the bonus content differs between the official EC and nationwide editions.
まあ皆さんこの際、どちらもゲットしちゃってください！
So everyone, please go ahead and get both of them on this occasion!
そして、冒頭にも言った重大発表がこちら！
And here is the major announcement we mentioned at the beginning!
アルバムのリード曲になっている「MAKE IT, BREAK IT」について続報があります！
We have an update on the album's lead track, "MAKE IT, BREAK IT"!
先ほど披露した6thシングル「MAKE IT, BREAK IT」のデジタルリリースが決定しました！
The digital release of our 6th single "MAKE IT, BREAK IT," which we just performed, has been confirmed!
デジタルリリースは明日、11月24日です！みんな絶対にチェックしてね！
The digital release is tomorrow, November 24th! Everyone, make sure to check it out!
そして、この「MAKE IT, BREAK IT」のMVの公開なんですが、普段やったら楽曲のリリースとほぼ同時に公開やねんけど
Also, about the release of the "MAKE IT, BREAK IT" music video... normally, it would be released almost at the same time as the song.
運営さんがですね、もっともっといいものにしたいということで、公開を延期することになりました！
However, the management wanted to make it even better, so they've decided to postpone its release!
そんなね、こちらのMVには、3Dになった...
And in this music video, we'll see the 3D versions of...
私たちが登場します！
We are making our appearance!
はい、皆さん、どんな内容に仕上がっているか
Yes, everyone! How is the content going to turn out?
今からめっちゃ楽しみにしててな！
Look forward to it so much starting from now!
イェーイ！踊ったもんね！
Yeah! We danced, didn't we?
ダンスとかもね、やったもんね。ダンスもね、やりましたよ。
We did dance and stuff, right? Yes, we danced.
はい、続いてはチハ、お願いします。
Okay, next up, Chiha, please go ahead.
はーい！それではこちらをご覧ください。どうぞ！
Sure! Please take a look at this. Here you go!
ホロカについてです！一昨日発売された、チハとニコのスタートデッキ、
It's about Holoka! The start decks for Chiha and Niko, released the day before yesterday,
実は今日のライブでお披露目した、新衣装のセカンドカードが収録されているんです！
actually include second cards of the new outfits revealed in today's live stream!
みんなにね、サプライズのつもりで、先行してセカンド衣装を入れてもらったんですが、びっくりしましたか？
We had the second outfits included beforehand as a surprise for everyone. Were you surprised?
びっくりしたよね。実はね、出てたんだよね。
You were surprised, right? Actually, it was already out.
これら2つのスタートデッキは、取り扱いのあるカードショップにて販売中です。気になった方はぜひ手にとってみてください！
These two start decks are on sale at participating card shops. If you're interested, please pick them up!
ホロカに関する情報はまだまだあります！こちらもご覧ください。どうぞ！
We still have more information about Holoka! Please take a look at this as well. Here you go!
来月19日発売の新ブースターパック「アヤカシバーミリオン」、その中に、
In the new booster pack 'Ayakashi Vermilion' releasing on December 19th,
今日、リちゃんがお披露目した新衣装のセカンドが収録されています！
the second card of the new outfit that Ri-chan revealed today is included!
え、マジ！？何それ、ええ、ちょっといいなぁ。
Wait, really?! What's that? Oh, I'm jealous.
スタッフさーん、ヴィヴィとスーちゃんのも早くお願いしますよー！
Staff members, please make Vivi's and Suu-chan's soon too!
お願いします、早く、早く！楽しみですね。
Please, do it quickly, quickly! We're looking forward to it.
はい、では続いてはスーちゃん、お願いします。
Alright, next up, Suu-chan, please go ahead.
はーい！ホロライブ公式ぬいぐるみブランド「hololive friends with u」、
Sure! The official Hololive plushie brand 'hololive friends with u',
通称「ホロフレ」に、ついに私たちFLOW GLOWの5人が登場します！
commonly known as 'Holo-Friends', finally features the five of us from FLOW GLOW!
やったー！ついにだ！
Yay! Finally!
今年のエキspoで開発中とお知らせしてから、やっと皆さんにお届けできるようになりました！
Since we announced they were in development at this year's Expo, we can finally bring them to you!
注目は髪型や衣装、とにかく再現度がすごい！
Pay attention to the hairstyles and outfits—the reproduction quality is amazing!
今日の22時より予約開始となりますので、お見逃しなく！
Reservations start tonight at 10 PM, so don't miss out!
続いてのグッズはこちら！
Next up is this merchandise!
今回お披露目した3Dの姿がアクリルスタンドになります！
Our newly revealed 3D forms are becoming acrylic stands!
先輩たちの3Dアクスタを持ってる人なら分かると思うんですが、かなり大きめのサイズとなっております。
If you own the 3D acrylic stands of our seniors, you'll know they are quite large in size.
存在感ばっちりな私たちの3Dアクスタ、ぜひ手にとめてください！
They have an outstanding presence, so please be sure to get our 3D acrylic stands!
こちらもホロフレと同じく今日の22時より予約開始となりますので、合わせてチェックしてくれると嬉しいです。
Just like Holo-Friends, reservations start tonight at 10 PM, so we'd appreciate it if you'd check them out too.
続いてはニコ、お願いします！
Next up, Niko, please go ahead!
はーい！池袋にある、まずはこちらをご覧ください。どうぞ！
Sure! Located in Ikebukuro... first, please take a look at this. Here you go!
（笑い声）
(Laughter)
池袋にある、池袋にあるタワーレコード渋谷... サンシャインシティアルパ店ほか、全国のタワーレコード12店舗、そこで！
Located in Ikebukuro... Tower Records Shibuya... Sunshine City Alpa store and other 12 Tower Records stores nationwide, there!
FLOW GLOWの1stアルバム発売を記念したポップアップの開催が決定！
A pop-up shop commemorating the release of FLOW GLOW's 1st album has been confirmed!
今まで公式オンラインでしか手に入らなかったミックステープの1、2のほか、先ほど紹介したFGのホロフレ、
In addition to Mixtapes 1 and 2, which were previously only available on the official online shop, and the Holo-Friends we introduced earlier,
グッズも盛りだくさんとなっております！
there will be plenty of other merchandise!
またですね、期間中にグッズをお買い上げの方にはノベルティももらえる予定となっておりますので、期間、1月20日から2月8日まで。
Also, during the period from January 20th to February 8th, those who purchase merchandise will receive a novelty item.
グッズに関する詳しい情報やノベルティ条件などについては、12月中旬開設予定の特設ページをご覧ください！
For detailed merchandise information and novelty requirements, please check the special page scheduled to open in mid-December!
最後はリオナ、お願いします。
Finally, Riona, please go ahead.
はーい！
Sure!
それでは、こちらをご覧ください。どうぞ！
Well then, please take a look at this. Here you go!
この後、FLOW GLOW公式チャンネルのメンバーシップにてアフタートークライブがあります！
After this, we will hold an After-Talk Live stream on our FLOW GLOW official channel membership!
そっちにも足を運びたいなぁというそこのあなた、ぜひ今のうちにメンバーシップの登録をお願いします。
If you are thinking, 'I want to go watch that too,' please register for the membership right now!
そのアフタートークライブは、ここではなく別のステージからお届けします。
This After-Talk Live stream will be broadcast from a different stage, not here.
そこでのみ聞けるライブの裏話とか、あとは1stアルバムに収録されている曲の中から、あの曲を披露したいと思います！
We'll talk about behind-the-scenes stories you can only hear there, and perform that song from our 1st album!
どう？ますます気になってきたんじゃない？
What do you think? Aren't you getting more and more interested?
気になる！待ってるからね。
I am! We'll be waiting for you.
また、私たち一人一人のチャンネルのメンバーシップでも「推しカメラ」配信もあります。
Also, there will be 'Oshi-Cam' streams on each of our personal membership channels.
ぜひ、そっちも覗きに来てね！
Please come take a look at those as well!
そして、12月9日からの定期配信は3Dとなります！
And, our regular streams starting from December 9th will be in 3D!
やったー！お楽しみに！
Yay! Look forward to it!
さあ、皆さん... 楽しい時間はあっという間ですね。
Well, everyone... fun times fly by so quickly.
そろそろライブも終了となります。
The live stream is about to end.
えー！やだやだ！誰か突っ込まないと終わる。
Eh?! No, no! If someone doesn't interject, it'll end.
ステージの上でね、写真に残したいんですけど。写真、写真！
We want to capture a photo on stage! Photo, photo!
撮ろう撮ろう！いい写真撮ろう。
Let's take one! Let's take a nice photo.
いい感じ、写ってる？写ってるよ。
Looks good, are we in the frame? Yes, we are.
じゃあ行くよ！はい、チーズ！パシャパシャパシャ！撮れた？みんな、撮れたかな？
Okay, here we go! Say cheese! *Click click click* Did you get it? Did everyone get it?
よし、ありがとう！
Great! Thank you!
スーちゃんよくやったね、ありがとう。
You did great, Suu-chan. Thank you.
スーちゃんのおかげでね、素敵な思い出も撮れたところで、ここでメンバー一人一人からファンの皆さんにメッセージをお届けしたいと思います。まずはスーちゃんから。
Thanks to Suu-chan, we captured a wonderful memory. Now, we'd like to deliver a message from each of us to all the fans. First, from Suu-chan.
はい、FLOW GLOW、そしてFLOWEE、ここまで一緒に走ってきてくれてありがとうございます。みんなのおかげで3Dになれたよ！
Yes! To FLOW GLOW and FLOWEE, thank you so much for running alongside us up to this point. Thanks to everyone, we were able to get 3D forms!
こっから先もいろんな思い出をみんなと一緒に作っていきたいです。よろしくお願いします。次はヴィヴィ！
From here on out, we want to create many more memories with all of you. We look forward to your support! Next up is Vivi!
はい！いつも応援してくださるフロールミの皆さん、そしてメンバーみんな、いつもありがとう！
Yes! To the Flowlumi supporting us, and to all the members, thank you always!
みんながいるからここまで来れました！
Because you were all here, we could make it this far!
2年目も、みんなと一緒にどんどん花道登っていきましょう！
In our second year, let's keep climbing the path of glory together!
これからもよろしくね！ほんまにありがとう！
Please keep supporting us! Thank you so much!
さあ、続きましてリコはどうですか？
Now, next, how about you, Riko?
FG、出会ってくれてありがとう。
FG, thank you for meeting me.
ありがとう。あ、こちらこそありがとう。
Thank you. Oh, thank you as well.
フログロウというダイヤモンドに気づけたあなた、天才じゃん！
You, who noticed the diamond that is Flow Glow, are a genius!
これからもよろしく、フロールミ！ありがとう！
Keep supporting us, Flowlumi! Thank you!
あ、はい、千早でございます。
Ah, yes, this is Chihaya.
いや本当にね、今日という日をこの5人で迎えられたことが本当に嬉しく思いますし、
Really, I am so happy that the five of us could welcome this day together...
このたくさんの方に我々のね、3Dお披露目を見守っていただけたことも本当に嬉しく思います。最後まで見ていただいてありがとうございます。
and I'm truly grateful that so many people watched over our 3D debut. Thank you for watching until the end.
ここからね、我々5人がもっともっと未来に向かって突き進んでいく姿、
From here on, the way the five of us push forward towards the future...
絶対に見逃さないでくださいね！今日は本当にありがとう！
make sure you don't miss it! Thank you so much for today!
メン限も待ってます！待ってるよ！
We're waiting in the membership-only streams too! We're waiting!
はい、最後、リッちゃん！
Alright, and finally, Ricchan!
はい！デビュー当時からずっと夢だった、歌って踊る姿を届けることができたことを、本当に嬉しく思います！
Yes! I'm truly happy that I could show you my singing and dancing, which has been my dream since our debut!
ここまで応援してくださって、本当にありがとうございました！
Thank you so much for supporting me up to this point!
そしてね、私たちはこれからも...
And, from now on, we will...
ちょっとおいでよ、ちょっとおいでよみんな。
Wait, come here, everyone, come here.
おお、いいこと言ってるのに！
Oh, she was saying something nice!
何その、まるでアンコールみたいな、やめてね。
What is that? Like an encore? Stop it.
あ、リオナが塞がれちゃった！あ、あ、あ！
Ah, Riona is blocked! Ah, ah, ah!
いやよ！私喋ってるじゃん！
No! I'm talking here!
ちょっと男子！ちょっと男子！一言ある？
Hey, boys! Hey, boys! Do you have a word?
まだ、やめて、ごめんね、喋っていい？
Wait, stop, sorry, can I talk?
あのね、これからもね、私たち一人一人の歩みをね、みんなにね、見守ってほしいな！
You see, from now on, I want everyone to watch over each of our paths!
だから、フログロウのこと、みんなこれからもよろしくね！よろしくね！
So, everyone, please support Flow Glow from now on! Please do!
はい、どうぞアンコール！あ、はい！
Alright, cue the encore! Ah, yes!
違う、違うって！
No, that's not it!
あ、バレてるバレてる、完全に。
Ah, we've been found out, completely.
ここじゃないか、ここじゃないって。ちょっと早かったかな。
Not here? No, not here. Maybe it was a bit too early.
お別れ？お別れする？
Goodbye? Should we say goodbye?
じゃあこれで終わりなの？これでおわりなの？
So this is the end? This is the end?
ちょっと...バイバイしよっか。
Wait... let's say bye-bye.
じゃあ最後に挨拶するね。そうだね。
So, let's do a final greeting. Yeah, let's.
それでは、私たち、せーの！
With that, we are... ready, set...
フログロウでしたー！
Flow Glow!
ありがとうございましたー！
Thank you so much!
ばいばいよー、んーー、まっ！
Bye-bye, mwah!
ばいばーい！大好きやで！ちゅっ！
Bye-bye! I love you! Chu!
本当にありがとう！んーー、まっ！
Thank you so much! Mwah!
え？！何それ？！何それ？！
What?! What was that?! What was that?!
ありがとう、んーー、まっ！
Thank you, mwah!
ありがとう。
Thank you.
フロールミ、アンコールありがとう！
Flowlumi, thank you for the encore!
今日は最高のライブでした！
Today was the best live show!
みんな楽しんでくれたかな？
Did everyone have fun?
最後は、やっぱりこの曲！
And for the end, of course, this song!
FG ROADSTER!
搭載V8エンジン
Equipped with a V8 engine
第7感持ってる原人
A primitive man with a seventh sense
Rockするこの世界と全人類
Rocking this world and all humanity
この5人でゲームをチェンジ
These five are changing the game
唸る4輪発射セヨ
The roaring four wheels, launch!
皆さん3キューサランヘヨ
Thank you everyone, Saranghaeyo!
操る2台のturntable
Controlling two turntables
獲る1番ここground 0 (aye)
Taking number one here at Ground Zero (aye)
リスク超えて挑戦
Overcoming risks to challenge
当選 チャンスもセットだ 当選
Winner! A chance is also included! Winner!
昇り上げる 頂点
Rising all the way to the top!
座布団積んでく 昇天
Piling up cushions and ascending to heaven!
乗り込め FG ROADSTER
Hop into the FG ROADSTER!
特殊部隊 集合 能力者
Special forces, assemble, ability users!
この歴史に名を掘る チョーカッコよく
Carving our names into history, super cool!
ぶっちぎりで置き去り カースタント
Leaving everyone in the dust with a car stunt!
いま高速で撃ち抜いていく大気圏
Now, piercing through the atmosphere at high speed!
エンジンからジェットの炎 濡れている回帰へ
Jet flames shooting from the engine, towards the wet regression!
がんがんに広がる体温 超えてく回帰線
Body temperature spreading intensely, crossing the regression line!
バックミラーにBIG BLUEが映ってる IPF, FIRE!
The BIG BLUE is reflected in the rearview mirror, IPF, FIRE!
ぶち上げたいから飛んでく ぶち散らせ
I want to get hyped up, so I'm flying off, scatter it all!
この燃料は朽ち果てない
This fuel will never run out!
夜勤レスで寿司食べたい
I want to eat sushi since I have no night shifts!
燃える世界ビジョン
A burning world vision!
燃やそう メンバー一同
Let's burn it up, all members together!
ただいま現在進行形 超えてく世界規模
Currently in progress, exceeding the world scale!
叶うはずだわ STAR
It's bound to come true, STAR!
心臓が MONSTER
My heart is a MONSTER!
エイリアンじゃ足りひんな
Even an alien isn't enough!
FG PARTY HIGH!
光る TESLA ROADSTER
Glowing TESLA ROADSTER!
HEAVY BOOSTER!
目覚めていく本能
Awakening instinct,
青い炎
blue flame!
BFF, LET'S GO OUT!
そう 蹴り上げろ ゼロから
So kick it up from zero!
空まで 囚われ
Captivated all the way to the sky,
走る FG ROADSTER
the FG ROADSTER runs!
うなる BOOSTER
Roaring BOOSTER!
ROAD, ROAD, ROAD, SPACE TO BE
いま CHASE ME!
Now, CHASE ME!
ターボにスーパーカー ハンドル捌く 9マッハ
Turbo and a supercar, handling at Mach 9!
服装重厚 チューバッカ
Fluffy, heavy clothing, Chewbacca!
次元が違う連中ばっか
Just a bunch of guys from a different dimension!
Hey コーナー攻めて ギリギリ
Hey, pushing the corners to the absolute limit!
モーター全開 ジリジリ
Motors at full throttle, sizzling!
ソーラーカーの道引き
Guided by the solar car,
大幅がピチピチ
massively fresh and lively!
タイヤ焦がして ドーナツターン
Burning tires with a donut turn!
弾け飛んでく ドラム缶
Drum cans bursting and flying away!
顧客満足度高くて ぶち上がってるお客さん
High customer satisfaction, our hyped-up guests!
ゼロから最高到達点
Reaching the highest point from zero!
貯める太陽光発電
Storing solar power generation!
探索するこの小惑星
Exploring this asteroid,
覚醒突入 ボーナスステージ
entering awakening, bonus stage!
一直線 伸びてる ROAD
A straight road stretching out!
VIBRATION, エンジンの鼓動
VIBRATION, the engine's heartbeat!
速度増し上がってる駆動
Speed-increasing drive,
臨界重力 凌駕、非日常
transcending critical gravity, an extraordinary experience!
開拓していくフロンティア
Pioneering the frontier,
旅立つ ROADSTER, ONLY ONE!
setting off on the ROADSTER, ONLY ONE!
アクセル踏み込んでいく ドンピシャ
Stepping on the accelerator, perfectly on target!
飛んでく日本一周
Flying on a tour around Japan!
1億馬力の中低音
100 million horsepower mid-low range!
火星のホテルが休憩所
Mars hotel is our rest stop!
並んで走行 UFO
UFOs cruising side-by-side,
降り立つ SPACE STATION
landing on the SPACE STATION!
物語は継承
The story is inherited!
まるで急送ステーション
Just like a rapid delivery station!
この先の席も成長
Growth even in the seats ahead!
生き延びて急加速 TAKEOFF!
Survive and rapidly accelerate, TAKEOFF!
叶うはずだわ STAR
It's bound to come true, STAR!
心臓が MONSTER
My heart is a MONSTER!
エイリアンじゃ足りひんな
Even an alien isn't enough!
FG PARTY HIGH!
光る TESLA ROADSTER
Glowing TESLA ROADSTER!
HEAVY BOOSTER!
目覚めていく本能
Awakening instinct,
青い炎
blue flame!
BFF, LET'S GO OUT!
そう 蹴り上げろ ゼロから
So kick it up from zero!
空まで 囚われ
Captivated all the way to the sky,
走る FG ROADSTER
the FG ROADSTER runs!
うなる BOOSTER
Roaring BOOSTER!
ROAD, ROAD, ROAD, SPACE TO BE
いま CHASE ME!
Now, CHASE ME!
以上、私たち
That's all from us,
FLOW GLOWでした！
FLOW GLOW!
ありがとうございました！
Thank you very much!
FLOW GLOW 3D LIVE 「MAKE IT. BREAK IT.」
FLOW GLOW 3D LIVE \"MAKE IT. BREAK IT.\"